question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Stevie Wonder's real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "John Williams composed the music for 'Star Wars'.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The 2011 movie 'The Adventures of Tin tin' was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they received.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The music video to The Buggle's 'Video Killed the Radio Star' was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song 'Do the Bartman'.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Korean girl group, TWICE, consists of 9 members",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The song 'Stronger Than You' is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
